aboutasiatravel.com 2012-06-08

# Privacy Policy

This document sets out how ABOUTAsia Travel Services Ltd (ABOUTAsia) uses and protects any information that you give ABOUTAsia when you use this website.

ABOUTAsia is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

ABOUTAsia may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1st September 2010.

## What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * Your name and title
  * Contact information including your email address
  * Demographic information such as your native language and the ages of your children
  * Information on your preferences and interests
  * The IP address of your computer

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping
  * Preventing fraud
  * Ensuring that our products best match your needs, and the needs of future guests
  * Identifying if our website is performing well, or needs altering to suit guest needs and preferences
  * If you choose to travel with us, we may occasionally send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting, using the email address which you have provided.
  * If you choose to travel with us, we may contact you afterwards for quality control purposes.
  * If you do not choose to travel with us, we may keep your records, so that we may help you more efficiently in the event of you deciding to travel in the future.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. 

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * If you book a tour with us, you may opt out of receiving any future promotional material
  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by emailing us at 

**We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties, unless we are required by law to do so.**

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please contact us 

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

_Please close this window and return to our main website for more[Cambodia travel advice, or to plan your Siem Reap or Angkor Wat vacation.](http://www.aboutasiatravel.com/)_
